tokens	ner_tags	text
['all', 'songs', 'written', 'by', 'm.o.d.', ',', 'unless', 'otherwise', 'stated']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-GRP', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	all songs written by m.o.d. , unless otherwise stated
['he', 'worked', 'in', 'a', 'bookstore', 'before', 'becoming', 'a', 'journalist', ',', 'first', 'for', 'le', 'devoir', ',', 'and', 'then', 'for', 'cité', 'libre', ',', 'for', 'which', 'he', 'later', 'became', 'the', 'director', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-GRP', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-GRP', 'I-GRP', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-CW', 'I-CW', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	he worked in a bookstore before becoming a journalist , first for le devoir , and then for cité libre , for which he later became the director .
['rinder', 'did', 'not', 'speak', 'on', 'camera', 'because', 'he', 'promised', 'his', 'first', 'interview', 'to', 'the', 'bbc', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-CORP', 'O']	rinder did not speak on camera because he promised his first interview to the bbc .
['in', '2010', ',', 'the', 'musical', 'instrument', 'maestro', 'raghav', 'sachar', 'was', 'the', 'highlight', 'of', 'the', 'event', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	in 2010 , the musical instrument maestro raghav sachar was the highlight of the event .
['she', 'became', 'opposed', 'to', 'abortion', 'in', '1992', 'while', 'attending', 'a', 'bible', 'study', 'and', 'has', 'since', 'spoken', 'out', 'about', 'how', 'abortion', 'has', 'negatively', 'impacted', 'her', 'life', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-CW', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	she became opposed to abortion in 1992 while attending a bible study and has since spoken out about how abortion has negatively impacted her life .
['for', 'example', ',', 'in', 'one', 'advertisement', 'a', 'woman', 'wearing', 'a', 'yellow', 'shirt', 'and', 'a', 'pin', 'is', 'juxtaposed', 'with', 'a', 'similarly', 'colored', 'piece', 'of', 'pie', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PROD', 'O']	for example , in one advertisement a woman wearing a yellow shirt and a pin is juxtaposed with a similarly colored piece of pie .
"['the', 'guardian', 'described', 'the', 'album', ""'s"", 'release', 'as', 'one', 'of', 'the', '50', 'key', 'events', 'in', 'the', 'history', 'of', 'r&b', 'and', 'hip', 'hop', '.']"	['B-GRP', 'I-GRP', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	the guardian described the album 's release as one of the 50 key events in the history of r&b and hip hop .
['the', 'gameplay', 'has', 'been', 'described', 'as', 'action', 'heavy', ',', 'and', 'compared', 'to', 'the', 'ratchet', '&', 'clank', 'series', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-CW', 'I-CW', 'I-CW', 'O', 'O']	the gameplay has been described as action heavy , and compared to the ratchet & clank series .
['it', 'was', 'developed', 'by', 'a', 'team', 'led', 'by', 'former', 'blizzard', 'entertainment', 'employees', ',', 'some', 'of', 'whom', 'had', 'overseen', 'the', 'creation', 'of', 'the', 'diablo', 'series', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-CORP', 'I-CORP', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-CW', 'O', 'O']	it was developed by a team led by former blizzard entertainment employees , some of whom had overseen the creation of the diablo series .
['the', 'play', 'interweaves', 'the', 'lives', 'of', 'the', 'poet', 'w.', 'h.', 'auden', 'and', 'the', 'mathematician', 'alan', 'turing', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'I-PER', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O']	the play interweaves the lives of the poet w. h. auden and the mathematician alan turing .
['the', '1988', 'elections', 'were', 'also', 'held', 'on', 'a', 'non', 'party', 'basis', ',', 'although', 'around', '30', 'candidates', 'sympathetic', 'to', 'the', 'muslim', 'brotherhood', 'were', 'elected', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-GRP', 'I-GRP', 'O', 'O', 'O']	the 1988 elections were also held on a non party basis , although around 30 candidates sympathetic to the muslim brotherhood were elected .
['she', 'fronted', 'the', 'band', 'gossip', 'from', 'its', 'formation', 'in', '1999', 'until', 'its', 'dissolution', 'in', '2016', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-GRP', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	she fronted the band gossip from its formation in 1999 until its dissolution in 2016 .
['of', 'the', '429', 'delegates', 'who', 'attended', ',', 'over', 'one', 'third', 'were', 'from', 'the', 'area', 'around', 'wheeling', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-LOC', 'O']	of the 429 delegates who attended , over one third were from the area around wheeling .
['in', 'doing', 'so', ',', 'he', 'reunited', 'with', 'former', 'high', 'school', 'and', 'college', 'teammate', 'malik', 'jackson', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O']	in doing so , he reunited with former high school and college teammate malik jackson .
['there', 'remained', 'the', 'question', 'of', 'whether', 'the', 'improved', 'performance', 'compared', 'to', 'the', 'automated', 'kh-8', 'gambit', '3', 'satellite', 'then', 'under', 'development', 'justified', 'the', 'cost', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PROD', 'I-PROD', 'I-PROD', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	there remained the question of whether the improved performance compared to the automated kh-8 gambit 3 satellite then under development justified the cost .
['the', 'group', 'smith', 'recorded', 'a', 'version', 'on', 'their', '1969', 'debut', 'album', ',', 'sung', 'by', 'gayle', 'mccormick']	['O', 'O', 'B-GRP', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PER', 'I-PER']	the group smith recorded a version on their 1969 debut album , sung by gayle mccormick
['in', 'previous', 'years', 'he', 'had', 'worked', 'with', 'alex', 'cox', 'on', 'the', 'soundtracks', 'of', 'his', 'films', 'sid', 'and', 'nancy', 'and', 'walker', 'in', '1986', 'and', '1987', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-CW', 'I-CW', 'I-CW', 'O', 'B-CW', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	in previous years he had worked with alex cox on the soundtracks of his films sid and nancy and walker in 1986 and 1987 .
['it', 'was', 'broadcast', 'on', 'the', 'channel', 'animal', 'planet', ',', 'with', 'episodes', 'having', 'aired', 'between', '2001', 'and', '2003', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-CORP', 'I-CORP', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	it was broadcast on the channel animal planet , with episodes having aired between 2001 and 2003 .
['it', 'stars', 'jeetendra', ',', 'moushumi', 'chatterjee', ',', 'govinda', ',', 'shilpa', 'shirodkar', 'with', 'music', 'composed', 'by', 'rajesh', 'roshan', '.']	['O', 'O', 'B-PER', 'O', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O', 'B-PER', 'O', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O']	it stars jeetendra , moushumi chatterjee , govinda , shilpa shirodkar with music composed by rajesh roshan .
['then', 'he', 'became', 'a', 'salesman', ',', 'and', 'later', 'a', 'public', 'relations', 'consultant', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PROD', 'I-PROD', 'O', 'O']	then he became a salesman , and later a public relations consultant .
['many', 'buildings', 'were', 'built', 'in', 'a', 'brick', 'nonplastering', 'style', 'characterized', 'by', 'a', 'special', 'kind', 'of', 'decorative', 'arts', 'using', 'colored', ',', 'figured', 'bricks', ',', 'usually', 'yellow', 'and', 'red', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-CW', 'I-CW', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	many buildings were built in a brick nonplastering style characterized by a special kind of decorative arts using colored , figured bricks , usually yellow and red .
['is', 'a', 'juku', 'in', 'tokyo', ',', 'established', 'over', '300', 'years', 'ago', '.']	['O', 'O', 'B-CORP', 'O', 'B-LOC', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	is a juku in tokyo , established over 300 years ago .
['the', 'city', 'is', 'also', 'home', 'to', 'via', 'university', 'college', 'which', 'brings', 'a', 'lot', 'of', 'international', 'students', 'to', 'move', 'to', 'this', 'town', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-GRP', 'I-GRP', 'I-GRP', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	the city is also home to via university college which brings a lot of international students to move to this town .
['fleur', 'live', 'stenogram', 'and', 'recording', 'at', 'echo', 'of', 'moscow', '(', 'rus', ')']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-CORP', 'I-CORP', 'I-CORP', 'O', 'O', 'O']	fleur live stenogram and recording at echo of moscow ( rus )
['vanadzor', '(', ')', 'is', 'an', 'urban', 'municipal', 'community', 'and', 'the', 'third', 'largest', 'city', 'in', 'armenia', ',', 'serving', 'as', 'the', 'capital', 'of', 'lori', 'region', 'in', 'the', 'northern', 'part', 'of', 'the', 'country', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-LOC', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-LOC', 'I-LOC', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	vanadzor ( ) is an urban municipal community and the third largest city in armenia , serving as the capital of lori region in the northern part of the country .
['lauren', 'jackson', 'has', 'won', 'the', 'award', 'four', 'times', ',', 'while', 'kelsey', 'griffin', 'has', 'won', 'the', 'award', 'three', 'times', '.']	['B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	lauren jackson has won the award four times , while kelsey griffin has won the award three times .
['401', 'designates', 'a', '373', 'cc', 'engine', ',', 'derived', 'from', 'the', 'ktm', '390', 'duke', 'of', 'street', 'bikes']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PROD', 'I-PROD', 'I-PROD', 'O', 'O', 'O']	401 designates a 373 cc engine , derived from the ktm 390 duke of street bikes
['however', 'she', 'has', 'to', 'settle', 'for', 'silver', 'medal', 'after', 'she', 'lost', 'to', 'akane', 'yamaguchi', 'in', 'a', 'tightly', 'contested', 'final', 'match', 'of', '3', 'games', '21', '–', '14', ',', '18', '–', '21', ',', '13', '–', '21', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	however she has to settle for silver medal after she lost to akane yamaguchi in a tightly contested final match of 3 games 21 – 14 , 18 – 21 , 13 – 21 .
['it', 'was', 'also', 'used', 'in', 'the', 'netflix', 'series', 'stranger', 'things', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-CORP', 'O', 'B-CW', 'I-CW', 'O']	it was also used in the netflix series stranger things .
['she', 'is', 'a', 'card', 'carrying', 'geek', 'and', 'considers', 'herself', 'boy', 'proof', ',', 'and', 'proud', 'of', 'it', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PROD', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	she is a card carrying geek and considers herself boy proof , and proud of it .
['he', 'is', 'the', 'co', 'founder', 'and', 'president', 'of', 'greentown', 'china', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-CORP', 'I-CORP', 'O']	he is the co founder and president of greentown china .
['duo', ',', 'with', 'michael', 'wollny', '(', 'piano', ')', ';', 'in', 'concert']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	duo , with michael wollny ( piano ) ; in concert
['jane', 'fonda', '–', 'julia', 'as', 'lillian', 'hellman']	['B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O', 'B-CW', 'O', 'B-PER', 'I-PER']	jane fonda – julia as lillian hellman
['on', 'the', 'first', 'episode', 'of', 'season', 'thirty', 'one', 'of', 'jeopardy!', ',', 'jeopardy', '!']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-CW', 'O', 'O', 'O']	on the first episode of season thirty one of jeopardy! , jeopardy !
['his', 'work', 'is', 'held', 'in', 'the', 'collections', 'of', 'the', 'j.', 'paul', 'getty', 'museum', ',', 'metropolitan', 'museum', 'of', 'art', ',', 'museum', 'of', 'fine', 'arts,', 'houston', ',', 'and', 'museum', 'of', 'modern', 'art', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-LOC', 'I-LOC', 'I-LOC', 'I-LOC', 'O', 'B-LOC', 'I-LOC', 'I-LOC', 'I-LOC', 'O', 'B-LOC', 'I-LOC', 'I-LOC', 'I-LOC', 'I-LOC', 'O', 'O', 'B-LOC', 'I-LOC', 'I-LOC', 'I-LOC', 'O']	his work is held in the collections of the j. paul getty museum , metropolitan museum of art , museum of fine arts, houston , and museum of modern art .
['after', 'a', 'long', 'break', ',', 'at', 'the', 'beginning', 'of', '1996', ',', 'he', 'issued', 'naposletku...', '(', 'after', 'all', '.', '.', '.', ')', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-CW', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	after a long break , at the beginning of 1996 , he issued naposletku... ( after all . . . ) .
['the', 'united', 'states', 'census', 'bureau', 'initially', 'defined', 'the', 'for', 'the']	['O', 'B-GRP', 'I-GRP', 'I-GRP', 'I-GRP', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	the united states census bureau initially defined the for the
['bbc', 'radio', '3', 'has', 'also', 'played', 'their', 'music', 'in', 'mainstream', 'programmes', '.']	['B-CORP', 'I-CORP', 'I-CORP', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	bbc radio 3 has also played their music in mainstream programmes .
['due', 'to', 'the', 'fact', 'that', 'there', 'are', 'two', 'different', 'materials', 'in', 'dfsw', ';', 'formation', 'of', 'a', 'composite', 'material', 'structure', 'within', 'the', 'nugget', 'zone', 'is', 'inevitable', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PROD', 'I-PROD', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	due to the fact that there are two different materials in dfsw ; formation of a composite material structure within the nugget zone is inevitable .
['one', 'of', 'his', 'doctoral', 'students', 'was', 'kazimierz', 'twardowski', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O']	one of his doctoral students was kazimierz twardowski .
['danses', 'concertantes', 'is', 'a', 'work', 'for', 'chamber', 'orchestra', 'by', 'igor', 'stravinsky', ',', 'composed', 'in', '1942', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	danses concertantes is a work for chamber orchestra by igor stravinsky , composed in 1942 .
['he', 'played', 'in', 'major', 'league', 'baseball', '(', 'mlb', ')', 'for', 'the', 'baltimore', 'orioles', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'B-CORP', 'I-CORP', 'I-CORP', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-GRP', 'I-GRP', 'O']	he played in major league baseball ( mlb ) for the baltimore orioles .
['odom', 'is', 'a', 'superfan', 'of', 'the', 'rock', 'band', 'night', 'ranger', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-GRP', 'I-GRP', 'O']	odom is a superfan of the rock band night ranger .
['welenchiti', 'is', 'served', 'by', 'a', 'railway', 'station', 'on', 'the', 'addis', 'ababa–djibouti', 'railway', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-LOC', 'I-LOC', 'I-LOC', 'O']	welenchiti is served by a railway station on the addis ababa–djibouti railway .
['the', 'main', 'works', 'were', 'at', 'irlam', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-LOC', 'O']	the main works were at irlam .
['in', '1613', ',', 'he', 'continued', 'his', 'education', 'at', 'university', 'of', 'basel', '(', 'where', 'his', 'grandfather', 'had', 'also', 'studied', ')', ',', 'in', 'geneva', 'and', 'sedan', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-GRP', 'I-GRP', 'I-GRP', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-LOC', 'O', 'B-LOC', 'O']	in 1613 , he continued his education at university of basel ( where his grandfather had also studied ) , in geneva and sedan .
['the', 'music', 'video', 'for', 'the', 'title', 'track', 'was', 'filmed', 'by', 'canon', 'inc.', 'as', 'a', 'campaign', 'for', 'their', '4k', 'canon', 'eos', 'c500', 'camera', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-CORP', 'I-CORP', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PROD', 'I-PROD', 'I-PROD', 'O', 'O']	the music video for the title track was filmed by canon inc. as a campaign for their 4k canon eos c500 camera .
['guinness', 'world', 'records', '2002', 'classified', 'it', 'as', 'the', 'most', 'valuable', 'tooth', ',', 'which', 'would', 'value', 'approximately', '£', '25,000', '(', '35,700', ')', 'in', 'late', '2001', '.']	['B-CW', 'I-CW', 'I-CW', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	guinness world records 2002 classified it as the most valuable tooth , which would value approximately £ 25,000 ( 35,700 ) in late 2001 .
['the', 'show', 'makes', 'extensive', 'use', 'of', '1980s', 'popular', 'music', ',', 'including', 'nena', '99', 'luftballons', ',', 'david', 'bowie', ',', 'new', 'order', 'and', 'eurythmics', 'among', 'others', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PER', 'B-CW', 'I-CW', 'O', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O', 'B-GRP', 'I-GRP', 'O', 'B-GRP', 'O', 'O', 'O']	the show makes extensive use of 1980s popular music , including nena 99 luftballons , david bowie , new order and eurythmics among others .
['it', 'fixed', 'some', 'bugs', 'and', 'added', 'support', 'for', 'half', 'height', 'floppy', 'drives', 'and', 'the', 'new', 'ibm', 'pcjr', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PROD', 'I-PROD', 'O']	it fixed some bugs and added support for half height floppy drives and the new ibm pcjr .
['parry', 'thomas', 'became', 'chief', 'engineer', 'at', 'leyland', 'motors', ',', 'a', 'company', 'whose', 'main', 'products', 'were', 'commercial', 'vehicles', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-CORP', 'I-CORP', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	parry thomas became chief engineer at leyland motors , a company whose main products were commercial vehicles .
['mongolia', 'has', 'an', 'embassy', 'in', 'tokyo', ',', 'established', 'in', '1973', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-LOC', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	mongolia has an embassy in tokyo , established in 1973 .
['in', '1923', ',', 'he', 'founded', 'the', 'organization', 'rodobrana', '(', 'home', 'guard', ')', ',', 'an', 'armed', 'militia', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-GRP', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	in 1923 , he founded the organization rodobrana ( home guard ) , an armed militia .
['he', 'was', 'a', 'versatile', 'actor', 'who', 'could', 'handle', 'with', 'ease', 'the', 'hand', 'fan', 'used', 'by', 'poor', 'scholars', 'and', 'pheasant', 'plumes', 'worn', 'by', 'generals', 'on', 'their', 'helmets', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PROD', 'I-PROD', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	he was a versatile actor who could handle with ease the hand fan used by poor scholars and pheasant plumes worn by generals on their helmets .
['porkins', 'has', 'gained', 'some', 'comedic', 'notoriety', 'due', 'to', 'his', 'size', ',', 'manner', 'and', 'untimely', 'death', ',', 'which', 'was', 'spoofed', 'in', 'the', 'family', 'guy', 'episode', 'blue', 'harvest', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-CW', 'I-CW', 'O', 'B-CW', 'I-CW', 'O']	porkins has gained some comedic notoriety due to his size , manner and untimely death , which was spoofed in the family guy episode blue harvest .
['eulenhald', 'near', 'waldleiningen', ',', '(', 'c', '.', '19', 'ha', ')', ',']	['O', 'O', 'B-LOC', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	eulenhald near waldleiningen , ( c . 19 ha ) ,
['runners', 'up', ':', 'chocolat', '•', 'france', 'and', 'camille', 'claudel', '•', 'france']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'B-CW', 'O', 'B-LOC', 'O', 'B-CW', 'I-CW', 'O', 'B-LOC']	runners up : chocolat • france and camille claudel • france
['his', 'son', ',', 'shintarō', 'hirase', ',', '(', '1884', '1939', ')', 'was', 'also', 'a', 'malacologist', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	his son , shintarō hirase , ( 1884 1939 ) was also a malacologist .
['while', 'auditioning', 'for', 'television', 'and', 'film', 'roles', ',', 'she', 'worked', 'on', 'theatre', 'productions', 'of', 'romeo', 'and', 'juliet', 'and', 'arsenic', 'and', 'old', 'lace', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-GRP', 'O', 'O', 'B-CW', 'I-CW', 'I-CW', 'O', 'B-CW', 'I-CW', 'I-CW', 'I-CW', 'O']	while auditioning for television and film roles , she worked on theatre productions of romeo and juliet and arsenic and old lace .
['each', 'key', 'has', 'a', 'cryptographic', 'state', 'as', 'defined', 'by', 'the', 'national', 'institute', 'of', 'standards', 'and', 'technology', '(', 'nist', ')', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-GRP', 'I-GRP', 'I-GRP', 'I-GRP', 'I-GRP', 'I-GRP', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	each key has a cryptographic state as defined by the national institute of standards and technology ( nist ) .
['the', 'road', 'fighting', 'championship', 'bantamweight', 'division', ',', 'with', 'upper', 'limit', 'at', '135.6', 'lb', '(', '61.5', 'kg', ')']	['O', 'B-CORP', 'I-CORP', 'I-CORP', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	the road fighting championship bantamweight division , with upper limit at 135.6 lb ( 61.5 kg )
"['it', 'was', 'the', 'world', ""'s"", 'first', 'computer', 'reservations', 'system', 'for', 'trains', '.']"	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PROD', 'I-PROD', 'I-PROD', 'O', 'O', 'O']	it was the world 's first computer reservations system for trains .
['michel', 'sanchez', ',', 'who', 'was', 'member', 'of', 'the', 'band', 'deep', 'forest', ',', 'co', 'wrote', 'the', 'lyrics', '.']	['B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-GRP', 'I-GRP', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	michel sanchez , who was member of the band deep forest , co wrote the lyrics .
['his', 'last', 'theatrical', 'composition', 'was', 'music', 'for', 'joan', 'the', 'woman', ',', 'starring', 'geraldine', 'farrar', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-CW', 'I-CW', 'I-CW', 'O', 'O', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O']	his last theatrical composition was music for joan the woman , starring geraldine farrar .
['he', 'is', 'known', 'for', 'presenting', 'the', 'nos', 'journaal', 'from', '1996', 'till', '2009', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-CW', 'I-CW', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	he is known for presenting the nos journaal from 1996 till 2009 .
['she', 'started', 'her', 'career', 'as', 'a', 'consultant', 'with', 'pricewaterhousecoopers', 'in', 'kenya', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-CORP', 'O', 'B-LOC', 'O']	she started her career as a consultant with pricewaterhousecoopers in kenya .
['bygrave', 'lives', 'in', 'queenscliff', 'with', 'her', 'husband', ',', 'multi', 'award', 'winning', 'writer', 'and', 'poet', 'barry', 'hill', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'B-LOC', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O']	bygrave lives in queenscliff with her husband , multi award winning writer and poet barry hill .
['a', 'new', 'recording', 'of', 'this', 'work', 'was', 'made', 'in', '1993', 'with', 'tom', 'waits', 'singing', 'along', 'with', 'the', 'original', 'recording', 'of', 'the', 'vagrant', 'during', 'the', 'final', 'section', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	a new recording of this work was made in 1993 with tom waits singing along with the original recording of the vagrant during the final section .
['he', 'has', 'previously', 'worked', 'at', 'networks', 'including', 'channel', '4', ',', 'itv', 'and', 'al', 'jazeera', 'english', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-CORP', 'I-CORP', 'O', 'B-CORP', 'O', 'B-CORP', 'I-CORP', 'I-CORP', 'O']	he has previously worked at networks including channel 4 , itv and al jazeera english .
['her', 'brother', 'was', 'the', 'conservative', 'party', 'politician', 'rab', 'butler', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-GRP', 'I-GRP', 'O', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O']	her brother was the conservative party politician rab butler .
['he', 'served', 'as', 'the', 'head', 'football', 'coach', 'at', 'allegheny', 'college', 'from', '2002', 'to', '2015', ',', 'compiling', 'a', 'record', 'of', '62', '–', '79', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-GRP', 'I-GRP', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	he served as the head football coach at allegheny college from 2002 to 2015 , compiling a record of 62 – 79 .
['she', 'recorded', 'jingles', 'for', 'major', 'companies', 'such', 'as', 'toyota', ',', 'american', 'airlines', ',', 'and', 'max', 'factor', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-CORP', 'O', 'B-CORP', 'I-CORP', 'O', 'O', 'B-CORP', 'I-CORP', 'O']	she recorded jingles for major companies such as toyota , american airlines , and max factor .
['the', 'game', 'is', 'based', 'upon', 'the', 'fantasy', 'novels', 'nine', 'princes', 'in', 'amber', '(', 'doubleday', '1970', ')', 'and', 'the', 'guns', 'of', 'avalon', '(', 'doubleday', '1972', ')', 'by', 'roger', 'zelazny', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-CW', 'I-CW', 'I-CW', 'I-CW', 'O', 'B-CORP', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-CW', 'I-CW', 'I-CW', 'I-CW', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O']	the game is based upon the fantasy novels nine princes in amber ( doubleday 1970 ) and the guns of avalon ( doubleday 1972 ) by roger zelazny .
['a', 'popular', 'use', 'is', 'rendering', 'an', 'animated', '3d', 'scene', 'as', 'an', 'adobe', 'flash', 'file', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-CW', 'I-CW', 'O', 'O']	a popular use is rendering an animated 3d scene as an adobe flash file .
['the', 'album', 'was', 'released', 'in', '1990', 'by', 'sparrow', 'records', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-CORP', 'I-CORP', 'O']	the album was released in 1990 by sparrow records .
['postman', 'pat', '(', '1981', ',', '1991', '–', '1994', ',', '1996', ',', '2004', '–', '2008', ')']	['B-CW', 'I-CW', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	postman pat ( 1981 , 1991 – 1994 , 1996 , 2004 – 2008 )
['aerogel', 'has', 'the', 'density', 'of', 'glass', ',', 'another', 'silicon', 'based', 'solid', 'to', 'which', 'it', 'may', 'be', 'compared', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PROD', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	aerogel has the density of glass , another silicon based solid to which it may be compared .
['the', 'film', 'had', 'musical', 'score', 'by', 'b.', 'a.', 'chidambaranath', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'I-PER', 'O']	the film had musical score by b. a. chidambaranath .
['pinky', 'wore', 'the', 'same', 'outfit', 'as', 'in', 'her', 'happy', 'days', 'episodes', ',', 'though', 'her', 'hair', 'was', 'now', 'in', 'a', '70s', 'style', 'shag', 'cut', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-CW', 'I-CW', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	pinky wore the same outfit as in her happy days episodes , though her hair was now in a 70s style shag cut .
"['a', '2014', 'rolling', 'stone', 'reader', ""'s"", 'poll', 'ranked', 'it', 'the', 'group', ""'s"", 'fourth', 'best', 'song', '.']"	['O', 'O', 'B-CW', 'I-CW', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	a 2014 rolling stone reader 's poll ranked it the group 's fourth best song .
['the', 'philippine', 'daily', 'inquirer', 'is', 'founded', 'and', 'publishes', 'its', 'first', 'issue', '.']	['O', 'B-GRP', 'I-GRP', 'I-GRP', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	the philippine daily inquirer is founded and publishes its first issue .
['tesla', '.', '(', 'defunct', ';', 'was', 'active', 'in', 'the', '1980s', 'and', '1990s', ')']	['B-CORP', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	tesla . ( defunct ; was active in the 1980s and 1990s )
['brian', 'j.', 'smith', '(', 'born', '1981', ')', ',', 'actor', ',', 'stargate', 'universe', ',', 'sense8']	['B-PER', 'I-PER', 'I-PER', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-CW', 'I-CW', 'O', 'B-CW']	brian j. smith ( born 1981 ) , actor , stargate universe , sense8
['tithes', ')', 'is', 'the', 'seventh', 'tractate', 'of', 'zeraim', '(', 'order', 'of', 'seeds', ')', 'of', 'the', 'mishnah', ',', 'tosefta', ',', 'and', 'the', 'jerusalem', 'talmud', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-CW', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-CW', 'O', 'B-CW', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-CW', 'I-CW', 'O']	tithes ) is the seventh tractate of zeraim ( order of seeds ) of the mishnah , tosefta , and the jerusalem talmud .
['de3', '–', '0-4-0', ',', '400', 'hp', ',', '50', 'tons', ',', '25', 'mph']	['O', 'O', 'B-PROD', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	de3 – 0-4-0 , 400 hp , 50 tons , 25 mph
['it', 'is', 'located', 'north', 'of', 'elgin', 'and', 'about', 'south', 'of', 'the', 'washington', 'border', ',', 'at', 'an', 'elevation', 'of', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-LOC', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-LOC', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	it is located north of elgin and about south of the washington border , at an elevation of .
['the', 'main', 'river', 'in', 'the', 'district', 'is', 'the', 'saale', 'with', 'wine', 'along', 'the', 'river', 'valley', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-LOC', 'O', 'B-PROD', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	the main river in the district is the saale with wine along the river valley .
['harvey', 'brooks', '–', 'bass', 'guitar', '(', 'highway', '61', 'revisited', ')']	['B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	harvey brooks – bass guitar ( highway 61 revisited )
['established', 'in', '1972', ',', 'the', 'pakistan', 'naval', 'air', 'arm', 'provides', 'fleet', 'air', 'defence', ',', 'maritime', 'reconnaissance', ',', 'and', 'anti', 'submarine', 'warfare', 'capability', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-GRP', 'I-GRP', 'I-GRP', 'I-GRP', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	established in 1972 , the pakistan naval air arm provides fleet air defence , maritime reconnaissance , and anti submarine warfare capability .
['for', 'example', ',', 'typical', 'fresh', 'chili', 'peppers', 'have', 'a', 'water', 'content', 'around', '90', '%', ',', 'whereas', 'tabasco', 'sauce', 'has', 'a', 'water', 'content', 'of', '95', '%', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PROD', 'I-PROD', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	for example , typical fresh chili peppers have a water content around 90 % , whereas tabasco sauce has a water content of 95 % .
"['it', 'is', 'the', 'fourth', 'single', 'from', 'the', 'former', 'duo', ""'s"", 'first', 'extended', 'play', 'bouquet', '.']"	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-CW', 'I-CW', 'B-CW', 'O']	it is the fourth single from the former duo 's first extended play bouquet .
['made', 'part', 'of', 'the', 'jilin–shulan', 'railway', 'in', '1941']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-LOC', 'I-LOC', 'O', 'O']	made part of the jilin–shulan railway in 1941
['he', 'was', 'a', 'member', 'of', 'the', 'federalist', 'party', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-GRP', 'I-GRP', 'O']	he was a member of the federalist party .
['president', 'in', ':', 'hot', 'shots!', 'part', 'deux', '(', 'film', ',', '1993', ')']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'B-CW', 'I-CW', 'I-CW', 'I-CW', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	president in : hot shots! part deux ( film , 1993 )
['randolph', 'was', 'born', 'in', 'nashville', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-LOC', 'O']	randolph was born in nashville .
['tex', 'beneke', '(', '1914', '–', '2000', ')', ',', 'big', 'band', 'saxophonist', ',', 'singer', ',', 'bandleader']	['B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	tex beneke ( 1914 – 2000 ) , big band saxophonist , singer , bandleader
['the', 'main', 'campus', 'of', 'mountains', 'of', 'the', 'moon', 'university', ',', 'a', 'private', 'university', ',', 'is', 'located', 'in', 'the', 'city', 'center', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-GRP', 'I-GRP', 'I-GRP', 'I-GRP', 'I-GRP', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	the main campus of mountains of the moon university , a private university , is located in the city center .
[';', 'voiced', 'by', 'brenda', 'vaccaro', 'in', 'season', '1', ';', 'rhea', 'perlman', 'in', 'season', '2']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O', 'O', 'O']	; voiced by brenda vaccaro in season 1 ; rhea perlman in season 2
['andrew', 'has', 'also', 'been', 'a', 'member', 'of', 'the', 'dallas', 'cowboys', ',', 'new', 'york', 'jets', ',', 'philadelphia', 'eagles', ',', 'and', 'minnesota', 'vikings', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-GRP', 'I-GRP', 'O', 'B-GRP', 'I-GRP', 'I-GRP', 'O', 'B-GRP', 'I-GRP', 'O', 'O', 'B-GRP', 'I-GRP', 'O']	andrew has also been a member of the dallas cowboys , new york jets , philadelphia eagles , and minnesota vikings .
['the', 'rolling', 'chassis', 'is', 'delivered', 'to', 'the', 'commercial', 'body', 'maker', ',', 'coachbuilder', ',', 'or', 'bulk', 'transporter', 'on', 'its', 'own', 'wheels', ',', 'under', 'its', 'own', 'power', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-CORP', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	the rolling chassis is delivered to the commercial body maker , coachbuilder , or bulk transporter on its own wheels , under its own power .
['thomas', 'christiansen', '–', 'vfl', 'bochum', ',', 'hannover', '96', '–', '2000', '–', '01', ',', '2002', '–', '06']	['B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O', 'B-GRP', 'I-GRP', 'O', 'B-GRP', 'I-GRP', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	thomas christiansen – vfl bochum , hannover 96 – 2000 – 01 , 2002 – 06
['it', 'is', 'located', 'in', 'the', 'municipality', 'of', 'rakovica', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-LOC', 'O']	it is located in the municipality of rakovica .
['it', 'was', 'released', 'in', '1969', 'on', 'atlantic', 'records', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-CORP', 'I-CORP', 'O']	it was released in 1969 on atlantic records .
['joseph', 'whitworth', 'devised', 'a', 'series', 'of', 'standards', 'for', 'engineering', ',', 'and', 'built', 'a', 'rifle', 'with', 'an', 'accurately', 'rifled', 'barrel', '.']	['B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	joseph whitworth devised a series of standards for engineering , and built a rifle with an accurately rifled barrel .
['the', 'third', ',', 'scherzo', 'like', 'movement', ',', 'has', 'an', 'easy', 'spirit', 'yet', 'is', 'full', 'of', 'complex', 'rhythms', 'and', 'interwoven', 'textures', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'B-CW', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	the third , scherzo like movement , has an easy spirit yet is full of complex rhythms and interwoven textures .
['a', 'zoetrope', 'is', 'a', 'device', 'used', 'for', 'animation', '.']	['O', 'B-PROD', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	a zoetrope is a device used for animation .
['the', 'demo', 'was', 'later', 'released', 'on', 'the', 'quadrophenia', 'box', 'set', 'of', '2011', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-CW', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	the demo was later released on the quadrophenia box set of 2011 .
['ocean', 'city', 'retains', 'its', 'ban', 'but', 'exempts', 'persons', 'with', 'a', 'concealed', 'weapons', 'permit', 'from', 'the', 'ban', '.']	['B-LOC', 'I-LOC', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	ocean city retains its ban but exempts persons with a concealed weapons permit from the ban .
['tremonti', ',', 'a', 'solo', 'project', 'by', 'the', 'above', 'musician']	['B-GRP', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	tremonti , a solo project by the above musician
['since', '2008', ',', 'he', 'has', 'been', 'the', 'senior', 'vice', 'president', 'of', 'disney', 'television', 'animation', '(', 'owned', 'by', 'the', 'walt', 'disney', 'company', ')', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-CORP', 'I-CORP', 'I-CORP', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-GRP', 'I-GRP', 'I-GRP', 'I-GRP', 'O', 'O']	since 2008 , he has been the senior vice president of disney television animation ( owned by the walt disney company ) .
['the', 'song', 'featured', 'chris', 'trousdale', 'from', 'dream', 'street', 'and', 'received', 'high', 'rotation', 'on', 'radio', 'disney', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O', 'B-GRP', 'I-GRP', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-CORP', 'I-CORP', 'O']	the song featured chris trousdale from dream street and received high rotation on radio disney .
['nostradameus', '(', 'paul', 'rugg', ')', 'claims', 'to', 'be', 'able', 'to', 'predictiate', 'the', 'future', ',', 'though', 'he', 'is', 'proven', 'wrong', 'on', 'occasion', '.']	['B-PER', 'O', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	nostradameus ( paul rugg ) claims to be able to predictiate the future , though he is proven wrong on occasion .
['rolls', 'collected', 'art', 'including', 'sketches', 'by', 'henry', 'fuseli', 'and', 'illuminated', 'manuscripts', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	rolls collected art including sketches by henry fuseli and illuminated manuscripts .
['jorge', 'martínez', 'de', 'hoyos', '(', 'el', 'abuelo', 'y', 'yo', ',', '1993', ')', 'and', 'ignacio', 'lópez', 'tarso', '(', 'de', 'pocas,', 'pocas', 'pulgas', ',', '2003', ')']	['B-PER', 'I-PER', 'I-PER', 'I-PER', 'O', 'B-CW', 'I-CW', 'I-CW', 'I-CW', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'I-PER', 'O', 'B-CW', 'I-CW', 'I-CW', 'I-CW', 'O', 'O', 'O']	jorge martínez de hoyos ( el abuelo y yo , 1993 ) and ignacio lópez tarso ( de pocas, pocas pulgas , 2003 )
['in', '1941', 'she', 'was', 'appointed', 'to', 'the', 'staff', 'of', 'the', 'royal', 'academy', 'of', 'music', 'where', ',', 'starting', 'with', 'seven', 'students', ',', 'she', 'built', 'the', 'drama', 'course', 'to', '70', 'students', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-GRP', 'I-GRP', 'I-GRP', 'I-GRP', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	in 1941 she was appointed to the staff of the royal academy of music where , starting with seven students , she built the drama course to 70 students .
"['top', '4', ':', ""don't"", 'stop', 'me', 'now', 'queen', '(', 'pop', 'jazz', ';', 'choreographer', ':', 'tba', ')']"	['O', 'O', 'O', 'B-CW', 'I-CW', 'I-CW', 'I-CW', 'B-GRP', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	top 4 : don't stop me now queen ( pop jazz ; choreographer : tba )
['karta', 'bink', 'was', 'born', 'in', 'commewijne', 'district', 'in', 'about', '1972', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-LOC', 'I-LOC', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	karta bink was born in commewijne district in about 1972 .
['hanriot', 'h', '.', '230', 'was', 'a', 'france', 'twin', 'engined', 'advanced', 'trainer', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-LOC', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	hanriot h . 230 was a france twin engined advanced trainer .
['mailen', 'auroux', 'maría', 'irigoyen', '6', '–', '1', ',', '2', '–', '6', ',', '[', '10', '–', '5', ']']	['B-PER', 'I-PER', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	mailen auroux maría irigoyen 6 – 1 , 2 – 6 , [ 10 – 5 ]
['they', 'also', 'manufacture', 'electronic', 'carillons', ',', 'street', 'clock', ',', 'glockenspiels', ',', 'and', 'monuments', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PROD', 'I-PROD', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	they also manufacture electronic carillons , street clock , glockenspiels , and monuments .
['its', 'design', 'is', 'based', 'on', 'the', '209', 'series', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PROD', 'I-PROD', 'O']	its design is based on the 209 series .
['its', 'northern', 'border', 'follows', 'interstate', '81', ',', 'and', 'its', 'eastern', 'border', 'follows', 'pennsylvania', 'route', '39', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-LOC', 'I-LOC', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-LOC', 'I-LOC', 'I-LOC', 'O']	its northern border follows interstate 81 , and its eastern border follows pennsylvania route 39 .
['capcom', 'purchased', 'the', 'intellectual', 'property', 'in', '2012', 'and', 'provided', 'funding', 'for', 'the', 'project', ',', 'reimagining', 'it', 'as', 'an', 'action-adventure', 'game', 'for', 'release', 'on', 'multiple', 'platforms', '.']	['B-CORP', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-CW', 'I-CW', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	capcom purchased the intellectual property in 2012 and provided funding for the project , reimagining it as an action-adventure game for release on multiple platforms .
['in', '1985', ',', 'he', 'tried', 'a', 'comeback', 'with', 'blue', 'bulls', ',', 'but', 'only', 'played', 'in', 'three', 'provincial', 'matches', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-GRP', 'I-GRP', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	in 1985 , he tried a comeback with blue bulls , but only played in three provincial matches .
['this', 'chiefly', 'consisted', 'of', 'coal', 'in', 'the', 'area', 'north', 'of', 'llanelli', 'and', 'around', 'saundersfoot', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-LOC', 'O', 'O', 'B-LOC', 'O']	this chiefly consisted of coal in the area north of llanelli and around saundersfoot .
['the', 'mill', 'property', 'was', 'added', 'to', 'the', 'national', 'register', 'of', 'historic', 'places', 'in', '1977', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-GRP', 'I-GRP', 'I-GRP', 'I-GRP', 'I-GRP', 'O', 'O', 'O']	the mill property was added to the national register of historic places in 1977 .
['he', 'finished', 'third', ',', 'behind', 'liberal', 'party', 'of', 'canada', 'nancy', 'karetak-lindell', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-GRP', 'I-GRP', 'I-GRP', 'I-GRP', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O']	he finished third , behind liberal party of canada nancy karetak-lindell .
['(', 'cannata', 'stayed', 'until', '1981', ',', 'returning', 'for', 'the', 'river', 'of', 'dreams', 'recording', 'sessions', 'in', '1993', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-CW', 'I-CW', 'I-CW', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	( cannata stayed until 1981 , returning for the river of dreams recording sessions in 1993 .
['the', 'keypad', 'lock', 'feature', 'found', 'on', 'most', 'mobile', 'phones', 'is', 'intended', 'to', 'help', 'prevent', 'accidental', 'dialing', ',', 'but', 'is', 'often', 'so', 'trivial', 'that', 'the', 'keypad', 'is', 'easily', 'pocket', 'unlocked', '.']	['O', 'B-PROD', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	the keypad lock feature found on most mobile phones is intended to help prevent accidental dialing , but is often so trivial that the keypad is easily pocket unlocked .
['evelyn', 'keyes', 'in', 'a', 'bit', 'part', '(', 'uncredited', ')']	['B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	evelyn keyes in a bit part ( uncredited )
['in', '1988', ',', 'it', 'was', 'adapted', 'into', 'a', 'funny', 'farm', ',', 'starring', 'chevy', 'chase', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-CW', 'I-CW', 'O', 'O', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O']	in 1988 , it was adapted into a funny farm , starring chevy chase .
['its', 'basement', 'hosts', 'kitchen', 'facilities', 'while', 'in', 'the', 'ground', 'floor', 'is', 'located', 'an', 'internet', 'café', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-CORP', 'I-CORP', 'O']	its basement hosts kitchen facilities while in the ground floor is located an internet café .
['sky', 'leads', 'the', 'cubs', 'to', 'the', 'mudflats', 'to', 'dig', 'up', 'clam', 'hiding', 'under', 'the', 'mud', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PROD', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	sky leads the cubs to the mudflats to dig up clam hiding under the mud .
['he', 'made', 'his', 'debut', 'for', 'sogndal', 'fotball', 'in', 'a', '1', '1', 'draw', 'against', 'ik', 'start', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-GRP', 'I-GRP', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-GRP', 'I-GRP', 'O']	he made his debut for sogndal fotball in a 1 1 draw against ik start .
['weight', 'tax', 'deduction', 'for', 'plug-in', 'hybrid', 'introduced']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PROD', 'I-PROD', 'O']	weight tax deduction for plug-in hybrid introduced
['remains', 'of', 'copper', 'smelting', 'sites', 'and', 'open', 'air', 'copper', 'mines', 'were', 'investigated', 'in', '1984', '–', '1985', '.']	['O', 'O', 'B-PROD', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	remains of copper smelting sites and open air copper mines were investigated in 1984 – 1985 .
"['after', 'the', 'film', ""'s"", 'release', ',', 'the', 'song', 'became', 'a', 'hit', 'and', 'a', 'jazz', 'standard', ',', 'and', 'has', 'been', 'widely', 'covered', '.']"	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-CW', 'I-CW', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	after the film 's release , the song became a hit and a jazz standard , and has been widely covered .
['a', 'few', 'days', 'later', ',', 'harry', 'houdini', 'comes', 'to', 'town', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	a few days later , harry houdini comes to town .
['according', 'to', 'his', 'employment', 'record', ',', 'he', 'worked', 'as', 'a', 'loader', 'for', 'the', 'united', 'parcel', 'service', 'from', '1983', 'to', '1997', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-CORP', 'I-CORP', 'I-CORP', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	according to his employment record , he worked as a loader for the united parcel service from 1983 to 1997 .
['torchlight', 'iii', ',', 'a', '2020', 'action', 'role', 'playing', 'game']	['B-CW', 'I-CW', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	torchlight iii , a 2020 action role playing game
['it', 'stars', 'shaina', 'magdayao', 'in', 'the', 'title', 'role', '.']	['O', 'O', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	it stars shaina magdayao in the title role .
['as', 'for', 'wheat', ',', 'another', 'staple', ',', 'it', 'took', 'another', 'three', 'or', 'four', 'thousand', 'years', '.']	['O', 'O', 'B-PROD', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	as for wheat , another staple , it took another three or four thousand years .
['he', 'moved', 'to', 'peru', 'for', 'eight', 'years', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'B-LOC', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	he moved to peru for eight years .
['in', '1997', ',', 'bbc', 'radio', '4', 'broadcast', 'a', 'dramatization', 'of', 'the', 'story', 'in', 'six', 'half', 'hour', 'episodes', ',', 'later', 're', 'edited', 'into', 'three', 'hour', 'long', 'episodes', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'B-CORP', 'I-CORP', 'I-CORP', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	in 1997 , bbc radio 4 broadcast a dramatization of the story in six half hour episodes , later re edited into three hour long episodes .
['he', 'moved', 'to', 'stockport', 'county', 'f.c.', ',', 'playing', '50', 'times', 'before', 'joining', 'tranmere', 'rovers', 'f.c.', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'B-GRP', 'I-GRP', 'I-GRP', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-GRP', 'I-GRP', 'I-GRP', 'O']	he moved to stockport county f.c. , playing 50 times before joining tranmere rovers f.c. .
['it', 'was', 'rebuilt', 'by', 'benjamin', 'ferrey', 'in', '1856', ',', 'on', 'the', 'site', 'of', 'an', 'earlier', 'church', ',', 'but', 'closed', 'in', '1970', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	it was rebuilt by benjamin ferrey in 1856 , on the site of an earlier church , but closed in 1970 .
"['horatio', 'allen', ',', 'designed', 'world', ""'s"", 'first', 'articulated', 'locomotive', 'in', '1832']"	['B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PROD', 'I-PROD', 'O', 'O']	horatio allen , designed world 's first articulated locomotive in 1832
['he', 'played', 'for', 'the', 'miami', 'dolphins', 'in', '1966', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-GRP', 'I-GRP', 'O', 'O', 'O']	he played for the miami dolphins in 1966 .
['sugar', 'sprinkled', 'on', 'cut', 'fruit', 'will', 'draw', 'out', 'the', 'water', 'through', 'hydrophilia', ',', 'making', 'the', 'fruit', 'mushy', 'and', 'wet', ',', 'as', 'in', 'a', 'common', 'strawberry', 'compote', 'recipe', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PROD', 'O', 'O']	sugar sprinkled on cut fruit will draw out the water through hydrophilia , making the fruit mushy and wet , as in a common strawberry compote recipe .
['shocking', 'blue', 'at', 'home', 'including', 'venus']	['B-GRP', 'I-GRP', 'B-CW', 'I-CW', 'O', 'B-CW']	shocking blue at home including venus
['two', 'of', 'the', 'awards', 'go', 'to', 'lundgaard', '&', 'tranberg', 'and', 'one', 'goes', 'to', '3xn', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-CORP', 'I-CORP', 'I-CORP', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-CORP', 'O']	two of the awards go to lundgaard & tranberg and one goes to 3xn .
['#', 'runaway', '(', 'del', 'shannon', ',', 'max', 'crook', ')', '–', '2', ':', '19']	['O', 'B-CW', 'O', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	# runaway ( del shannon , max crook ) – 2 : 19
['a', 'force', 'play', 'provided', 'the', 'second', 'out', 'of', 'the', 'inning', 'but', 'boog', 'powell', 'single', 'drove', 'in', 'one', 'run', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	a force play provided the second out of the inning but boog powell single drove in one run .
"['in', '2010', ',', 'sony', 'pictures', 'television', ',', 'the', 'show', ""'s"", 'production', 'company', ',', 'released', 'an', 'adaptation', 'for', 'the', 'iphone', ',', 'ipod', 'touch', ',', 'and', 'ipad', '.']"	['O', 'O', 'O', 'B-GRP', 'I-GRP', 'I-GRP', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PROD', 'O', 'B-PROD', 'I-PROD', 'O', 'O', 'B-PROD', 'O']	in 2010 , sony pictures television , the show 's production company , released an adaptation for the iphone , ipod touch , and ipad .
['starring', 'bing', 'crosby', 'and', 'dorothy', 'lamour', ',', 'it', 'is', 'a', 'musical', 'film', 'directed', 'by', 'a.', 'edward', 'sutherland', '.']	['O', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-CW', 'I-CW', 'O', 'O', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'I-PER', 'O']	starring bing crosby and dorothy lamour , it is a musical film directed by a. edward sutherland .
['jwpce', 'can', 'also', 'display', 'kanji', 'in', 'a', 'list', 'you', 'generate', 'in', 'a', 'different', 'color', 'so', 'that', 'it', 'colors', 'either', 'the', 'kanji', 'that', 'the', 'user', 'does', 'not', 'know', 'or', 'that', 'the', 'user', 'does', 'know', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PROD', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	jwpce can also display kanji in a list you generate in a different color so that it colors either the kanji that the user does not know or that the user does know .
['liverpool', 'also', 'suffered', 'severely', ',', 'with', 'many', 'shipwrecks', 'and', 'structural', 'damage', 'resulting', 'from', 'strong', 'winds', '.', '120', 'people', 'died', 'as', 'a', 'result', 'of', 'such', 'accidents', 'in', 'the', 'city', 'alone', '.']	['B-LOC', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	liverpool also suffered severely , with many shipwrecks and structural damage resulting from strong winds . 120 people died as a result of such accidents in the city alone .
['kemco', 'started', 'by', 'developing', 'video', 'games', 'for', 'the', 'nintendo', 'entertainment', 'system', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PROD', 'I-PROD', 'I-PROD', 'O']	kemco started by developing video games for the nintendo entertainment system .
['#', 'love', 'for', 'sale', '(', 'cole', 'porter', ')', '7', ':', '00']	['O', 'B-CW', 'I-CW', 'I-CW', 'O', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	# love for sale ( cole porter ) 7 : 00
['it', 'has', 'an', 'improved', 'camera', 'and', 'lens', ',', 'an', 'improved', 'screen', ',', 'battery', 'and', 'improved', 'interface', 'than', 'previous', 'model', 'samsung', 's5560', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PROD', 'I-PROD', 'O']	it has an improved camera and lens , an improved screen , battery and improved interface than previous model samsung s5560 .
['he', 'was', 'a', 'founding', 'member', 'of', 'the', 'société', 'française', 'de', 'photographie', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-GRP', 'I-GRP', 'I-GRP', 'I-GRP', 'O']	he was a founding member of the société française de photographie .
['the', 'structure', 'was', 'built', 'of', 'steel', ',', 'reinforced', 'concrete', ',', 'and', 'brick', ',', 'with', 'a', 'handsomely', 'designed', 'ivory', 'colored', 'terracotta', 'front', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PROD', 'O', 'O']	the structure was built of steel , reinforced concrete , and brick , with a handsomely designed ivory colored terracotta front .
['it', 'was', 'released', 'on', 'harvest', '/', 'emi', 'as', 'a', 'single', 'in', '1988', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-CORP', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-CW', 'O', 'O', 'O']	it was released on harvest / emi as a single in 1988 .
['it', 'was', 'later', 'the', 'home', 'field', 'of', 'the', 'calgary', 'vipers', 'baseball', 'team', 'of', 'the', 'north', 'american', 'league', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-GRP', 'I-GRP', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-GRP', 'I-GRP', 'I-GRP', 'O']	it was later the home field of the calgary vipers baseball team of the north american league .
['jagertee', '(', 'also', 'jägertee', ')', 'is', 'an', 'alcoholic', 'punch', 'historically', 'made', 'by', 'mixing', 'stroh', 'with', 'spiced', 'black', 'tea', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-CORP', 'O', 'O', 'B-PROD', 'I-PROD', 'O']	jagertee ( also jägertee ) is an alcoholic punch historically made by mixing stroh with spiced black tea .
['the', 'lead', 'single', ',', 'la', 'puerta', 'del', 'cielo', '/', 'seven', 'lives', ',', 'is', 'a', 'fusion', 'of', 'modern', 'and', 'classical', 'elements', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-CW', 'I-CW', 'I-CW', 'I-CW', 'I-CW', 'I-CW', 'I-CW', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	the lead single , la puerta del cielo / seven lives , is a fusion of modern and classical elements .
['kate', 'markowitz', 'harmony', 'vocals', '(', '1', ',', '4', ')', ',', 'background', 'vocals']	['B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	kate markowitz harmony vocals ( 1 , 4 ) , background vocals
['young', 'has', 'stated', 'in', 'concert', 'that', 'he', 'wrote', 'the', 'song', 'while', 'studying', 'history', 'in', 'high', 'school', 'in', 'winnipeg', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-LOC', 'O']	young has stated in concert that he wrote the song while studying history in high school in winnipeg .
['the', 'programme', 'attracted', 'high', 'ratings', 'for', 'the', 'then', 'new', 'channel', '4', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-CORP', 'I-CORP', 'O']	the programme attracted high ratings for the then new channel 4 .
['in', '1799', 'he', 'took', 'part', 'of', 'the', 'reduction', 'of', 'the', 'island', 'of', 'sri', 'lanka', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-LOC', 'I-LOC', 'O']	in 1799 he took part of the reduction of the island of sri lanka .
"['au', 'jardin', 'de', 'l', 'enfance', ',', '6', 'pieces', 'after', ""l'art"", ""d'être"", 'grand-père', 'by', 'victor', 'hugo', '.']"	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-CW', 'I-CW', 'I-CW', 'O', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O']	au jardin de l enfance , 6 pieces after l'art d'être grand-père by victor hugo .
['on', 'telegram', ',', 'a', 'white', 'supremacist', 'channel', 'encouraged', 'members', 'to', 'distribute', 'the', 'propaganda', '.']	['O', 'B-CW', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	on telegram , a white supremacist channel encouraged members to distribute the propaganda .
['american', 'high', 'commissioner', 'mark', 'w.', 'clark', '(', '1945', '–', '1947', ')']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'I-PER', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	american high commissioner mark w. clark ( 1945 – 1947 )
['jordan', 'also', 'played', 'the', 'ex', 'boyfriend', 'in', 'lily', 'allen', 'music', 'video', 'smile', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O', 'O', 'B-CW', 'O']	jordan also played the ex boyfriend in lily allen music video smile .
['the', 'station', 'is', 'owned', 'by', 'cumulus', 'media', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-CORP', 'I-CORP', 'O']	the station is owned by cumulus media .
['the', 'race', 'started', 'in', 'compiègne', 'and', 'finished', 'in', 'roubaix', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-LOC', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-LOC', 'O']	the race started in compiègne and finished in roubaix .
['zarm', '–', 'a', 'lunar', 'rescue', 'clone', '(', 'bbc', 'only', ')']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'B-CW', 'I-CW', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	zarm – a lunar rescue clone ( bbc only )
['fashion', 'had', 'achieved', 'what', 'is', 'now', 'known', 'as', 'the', 'victorian', 'fashion', 'silhouette', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PROD', 'I-PROD', 'O', 'O']	fashion had achieved what is now known as the victorian fashion silhouette .
['cream', 'was', 'sent', 'to', 'the', 'butter', 'factory', 'at', 'wowan', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-LOC', 'O']	cream was sent to the butter factory at wowan .
['guardians', 'of', 'the', 'galaxy', '–', 'stephane', 'ceretti', ',', 'nicolas', 'aithadi', ',', 'jonathan', 'fawkner', ',', 'and', 'paul', 'corbould']	['B-CW', 'I-CW', 'I-CW', 'I-CW', 'O', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O', 'O', 'B-PER', 'I-PER']	guardians of the galaxy – stephane ceretti , nicolas aithadi , jonathan fawkner , and paul corbould
['malone', 'attended', 'the', 'university', 'of', 'louisville', ',', 'where', 'he', 'played', 'baseball', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'B-GRP', 'I-GRP', 'I-GRP', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	malone attended the university of louisville , where he played baseball .
['300', 'meters', 'outside', 'barisha', ',', 'harem', 'district', ',', 'idlib', 'governorate']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'B-LOC', 'O', 'B-LOC', 'I-LOC', 'O', 'B-LOC', 'I-LOC']	300 meters outside barisha , harem district , idlib governorate
['co', 'lead', 'singer', 'mike', 'harrison', 'left', 'the', 'band', 'following', 'the', 'release', 'of', 'the', 'album', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	co lead singer mike harrison left the band following the release of the album .
['since', 'the', 'flavour', 'and', 'appeal', 'largely', 'depend', 'on', 'freshness', ',', 'commercial', 'producers', 'have', 'to', 'compensate', 'by', 'using', 'food', 'additive', 'as', 'well', 'as', 'imaginative', 'labeling', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PROD', 'I-PROD', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	since the flavour and appeal largely depend on freshness , commercial producers have to compensate by using food additive as well as imaginative labeling .
['1972', 'singles', 'chart', 'archive', 'at', 'the', 'official', 'charts', 'company', '(', 'click', 'on', 'relevant', 'week', ')']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-CORP', 'I-CORP', 'I-CORP', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	1972 singles chart archive at the official charts company ( click on relevant week )
['the', 'ships', 'carried', 'a', 'maximum', 'of', 'of', 'fuel', 'oil', 'that', 'gave', 'them', 'a', 'range', 'of', 'at', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PROD', 'I-PROD', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	the ships carried a maximum of of fuel oil that gave them a range of at .
['the', 'ashmolean', 'museum', 'in', 'oxford', 'has', 'a', 'further', '17', 'landscape', 'drawings', '.']	['O', 'B-LOC', 'I-LOC', 'O', 'B-LOC', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	the ashmolean museum in oxford has a further 17 landscape drawings .
['all', 'four', 'of', 'his', 'grandparents', 'were', 'catholic', 'church', 'immigrants', 'from', 'germany', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-GRP', 'I-GRP', 'O', 'O', 'B-LOC', 'O']	all four of his grandparents were catholic church immigrants from germany .
['in', '2014', ',', 'he', 'had', 'a', 'cameo', 'appearance', 'in', 'the', 'film', 'dumb', 'and', 'dumber', 'to', ',', 'starring', 'jim', 'carrey', 'and', 'jeff', 'daniels', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-CW', 'I-CW', 'I-CW', 'I-CW', 'O', 'O', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O']	in 2014 , he had a cameo appearance in the film dumb and dumber to , starring jim carrey and jeff daniels .
['it', 'was', 'the', 'county', 'seat', 'from', '1885', 'to', '1919', ',', 'when', 'the', 'government', 'moved', 'to', 'the', 'current', 'county', 'seat', 'of', 'finley', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'B-LOC', 'I-LOC', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-LOC', 'O']	it was the county seat from 1885 to 1919 , when the government moved to the current county seat of finley .
['a', 'few', 'had', 'tire', 'problems', 'including', 'kurt', 'busch', ',', 'joey', 'logano', ',', 'and', 'brad', 'keselowski', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O', 'O', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O']	a few had tire problems including kurt busch , joey logano , and brad keselowski .
['a', 'routing', 'table', 'is', 'analogous', 'to', 'a', 'distribution', 'map', 'in', 'package', 'delivery', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-CORP', 'I-CORP', 'O']	a routing table is analogous to a distribution map in package delivery .
"['the', 'company', ""'s"", 'primary', 'focus', 'is', 'praline', '(', 'chocolate', 'shells', 'with', 'soft', 'fillings', ')', ',', 'but', 'they', 'also', 'sell', 'marzipan', ',', 'solid', 'chocolates', ',', 'and', 'other', 'confectionery', '.']"	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PROD', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PROD', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	the company 's primary focus is praline ( chocolate shells with soft fillings ) , but they also sell marzipan , solid chocolates , and other confectionery .
['arsenal', 'goalkeeper', 'rami', 'shaaban', 'was', 'substituted', 'before', 'the', 'start', 'of', 'the', 'second', 'half', ',', 'having', 'pulled', 'a', 'thigh', 'muscle', '.']	['O', 'O', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	arsenal goalkeeper rami shaaban was substituted before the start of the second half , having pulled a thigh muscle .
"['her', 'brother', 'jackie', 'levy', 'served', 'as', 'mayor', 'of', 'beit', ""she'an"", 'for', 'the', 'likud', '.']"	['O', 'O', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-LOC', 'I-LOC', 'O', 'O', 'B-GRP', 'O']	her brother jackie levy served as mayor of beit she'an for the likud .
"['the', 'interior', 'was', 'designed', 'so', 'that', 'the', 'driver', ""'s"", 'seating', 'position', 'was', 'virtually', 'the', 'same', 'as', 'in', 'a', 'sedan', '.']"	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PROD', 'O']	the interior was designed so that the driver 's seating position was virtually the same as in a sedan .
['public', 'transport', 'is', 'integrated', 'into', 'the', 'verkehrsverbund', 'rhein-neckar', ',', 'whose', 'fares', 'therefore', 'apply', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-GRP', 'I-GRP', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	public transport is integrated into the verkehrsverbund rhein-neckar , whose fares therefore apply .
['the', 'kola', 'nut', 'is', 'also', 'mentioned', 'in', 'the', 'color', 'purple', 'by', 'alice', 'walker', ',', 'although', 'it', 'is', 'spelled', 'cola', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-CW', 'I-CW', 'I-CW', 'O', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	the kola nut is also mentioned in the color purple by alice walker , although it is spelled cola .
['poe', 'lived', 'in', 'baltimore', 'for', 'a', 'time', 'and', 'is', 'buried', 'there', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'B-LOC', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	poe lived in baltimore for a time and is buried there .
['the', 'video', 'also', 'features', 'a', 'cameo', 'appearance', 'from', 'close', 'friend', 'and', 'fellow', 'brooklyn', 'rapper', 'the', 'notorious', 'b.i.g.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-LOC', 'O', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'I-PER']	the video also features a cameo appearance from close friend and fellow brooklyn rapper the notorious b.i.g.
['throughout', 'the', 'album', ',', 'the', 'group', 'blends', 'their', 'brand', 'of', 'intelligence', ',', 'reflection', 'and', 'positivity', 'with', 'humorous', 'anecdote', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-CW', 'O']	throughout the album , the group blends their brand of intelligence , reflection and positivity with humorous anecdote .
['he', 'then', 'went', 'on', 'to', 'play', 'for', 'fc', 'auch', 'gers', 'between', '2006', 'and', '2008', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-GRP', 'I-GRP', 'I-GRP', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	he then went on to play for fc auch gers between 2006 and 2008 .
['belgian', 'albéric', 'schotte', 'won', 'the', 'race', 'in', 'a', 'four', 'man', 'sprint', '.']	['O', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	belgian albéric schotte won the race in a four man sprint .
['the', 'missiles', 'were', 'test', 'fired', 'from', 'a', 'hal', 'rudra', ';', 'two', 'missiles', 'succeeded', 'in', 'hitting', 'the', 'targets', 'at', 'a', 'range', 'of', '7', 'km', ',', 'while', 'one', 'reportedly', 'missed', 'the', 'target', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PROD', 'I-PROD', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	the missiles were test fired from a hal rudra ; two missiles succeeded in hitting the targets at a range of 7 km , while one reportedly missed the target .
['perry', 'entered', 'the', 'stadium', 'riding', 'atop', 'a', 'large', ',', 'golden', 'mechanical', 'lion', ',', 'opening', 'her', 'set', 'with', 'a', 'performance', 'of', 'roar', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-CW', 'O']	perry entered the stadium riding atop a large , golden mechanical lion , opening her set with a performance of roar .
['it', 'was', 'developed', 'by', 'the', 'chicago', 'mercantile', 'exchange', 'in', '1988', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-CORP', 'I-CORP', 'I-CORP', 'O', 'O', 'O']	it was developed by the chicago mercantile exchange in 1988 .
['children', 'coming', 'home', 'from', 'school', 'stop', 'to', 'stare', 'at', 'him', 'as', 'he', 'works', ',', 'impressed', 'by', 'the', 'roaring', 'bellows', 'and', 'burning', 'sparks', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PROD', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	children coming home from school stop to stare at him as he works , impressed by the roaring bellows and burning sparks .
['file', ':', 'dynix', 'search', 'results', '.', 'jpg', '|', 'dynix', 'showing', 'the', 'results', 'from', 'a', 'by', 'author', 'search', 'for', 'ernest', 'hemingway', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O']	file : dynix search results . jpg | dynix showing the results from a by author search for ernest hemingway .
['director', 'chuck', 'russell', 'served', 'as', 'an', 'executive', 'producer', ',', 'while', 'his', 'long', 'time', 'collaborator', 'frank', 'darabont', 'served', 'as', 'a', 'production', 'assistant', '.']	['O', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	director chuck russell served as an executive producer , while his long time collaborator frank darabont served as a production assistant .
['meteor', 'garden', 'using', 'on', 'the', 'word', 'gardener']	['B-CW', 'I-CW', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	meteor garden using on the word gardener
['she', 'was', 'on', 'the', 'faculty', 'at', 'university', 'of', 'oregon', 'for', 'over', 'two', 'decades', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-GRP', 'I-GRP', 'I-GRP', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	she was on the faculty at university of oregon for over two decades .
['other', 'stars', 'of', 'the', 'film', 'were', 'elizabeth', 'allan', ',', 'margot', 'grahame', ',', 'akim', 'tamiroff', ',', 'fay', 'bainter', 'and', 'eric', 'blore', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O']	other stars of the film were elizabeth allan , margot grahame , akim tamiroff , fay bainter and eric blore .
"['the', 'airport', ""'s"", 'simultaneous', 'remote', 'location', 'and', 'close', 'proximity', 'to', 'the', 'dallas–fort', 'worth', 'metroplex', 'were', 'major', 'factors', 'in', 'the', 'company', ""'s"", 'decision', 'to', 'conduct', 'experiments', 'there', '.']"	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-LOC', 'I-LOC', 'I-LOC', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	the airport 's simultaneous remote location and close proximity to the dallas–fort worth metroplex were major factors in the company 's decision to conduct experiments there .
['it', 'is', 'also', 'used', 'in', 'cosmetics', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PROD', 'O']	it is also used in cosmetics .
['hamamatsu', 'is', 'a', 'member', 'of', 'the', 'world', 'health', 'organization', '’s', 'alliance', 'for', 'healthy', 'cities', '(', 'afhc', ')', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-GRP', 'I-GRP', 'I-GRP', 'O', 'B-GRP', 'I-GRP', 'I-GRP', 'I-GRP', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	hamamatsu is a member of the world health organization ’s alliance for healthy cities ( afhc ) .
['signed', 'and', 'released', 'an', 'album', 'with', 'sony', 'music', 'in', '2007', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-CORP', 'I-CORP', 'O', 'O', 'O']	signed and released an album with sony music in 2007 .
['ekeroth', 'joined', 'the', 'sweden', 'democrats', 'in', '2006', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'B-GRP', 'I-GRP', 'O', 'O', 'O']	ekeroth joined the sweden democrats in 2006 .
"['based', 'on', 'pictures', 'from', 'the', ""insects'"", 'life', 'by', 'karel', 'čapek', 'and', 'josef', 'čapek']"	['O', 'O', 'B-CW', 'I-CW', 'I-CW', 'I-CW', 'I-CW', 'O', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O', 'B-PER', 'I-PER']	based on pictures from the insects' life by karel čapek and josef čapek
"['the', 'island', 'is', 'north', 'of', 'the', 'country', ""'s"", 'capital', ',', 'malé', '.']"	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-LOC', 'O']	the island is north of the country 's capital , malé .
['the', 'series', 'is', 'participated', 'in', 'by', 'multiple', 'manufacturers', ',', 'including', 'jaguar', 'racing', ',', 'audi', ',', 'nissan', ',', 'bmw', 'and', 'mahindra', '&', 'mahindra', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-GRP', 'I-GRP', 'O', 'B-CORP', 'O', 'B-CORP', 'O', 'B-CORP', 'O', 'B-CORP', 'I-CORP', 'I-CORP', 'O']	the series is participated in by multiple manufacturers , including jaguar racing , audi , nissan , bmw and mahindra & mahindra .
"['panagi', 'is', 'a', 'product', 'of', 'olympiakos', 'nicosia', 'fc', 'academies', 'and', 'in', '2010', 'he', 'was', 'promoted', 'to', 'the', 'men', ""'s"", 'team', 'by', 'coach', 'pambos', 'christodoulou', '.']"	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-GRP', 'I-GRP', 'I-GRP', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O']	panagi is a product of olympiakos nicosia fc academies and in 2010 he was promoted to the men 's team by coach pambos christodoulou .
['there', 'is', 'also', 'one', 'with', 'tupac', 'shakur', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O']	there is also one with tupac shakur .
['pozdrav', 'milici', 'stojadinović', 'srpkinji', ',', 'biography', '(', 'prometej', ',', 'novi', 'sad', ',', '2019', ')']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-LOC', 'I-LOC', 'O', 'O', 'O']	pozdrav milici stojadinović srpkinji , biography ( prometej , novi sad , 2019 )
['her', 'film', 'career', 'includes', 'roles', 'in', 'the', 'greek', 'tycoon', 'and', 'cliff', 'twemlow', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-CW', 'I-CW', 'I-CW', 'O', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O']	her film career includes roles in the greek tycoon and cliff twemlow .
"['the', 'plant', 'has', 'the', 'flexibility', 'to', 'build', 'any', 'of', 'the', 'company', ""'s"", 'front', 'engine', '/', 'front', 'wheel', 'drive', 'vehicles', 'in', 'a-segment', ',', 'b-segment', ',', 'or', 'c-segment', '.']"	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PROD', 'O', 'B-PROD', 'O', 'O', 'B-PROD', 'O']	the plant has the flexibility to build any of the company 's front engine / front wheel drive vehicles in a-segment , b-segment , or c-segment .
['wizkids', 'has', 'released', 'collectible', 'miniatures', 'of', 'the', 'turrets', ',', 'cores', 'and', 'companion', 'cube', '(', 's', ')', 'within', 'the', 'game', '.']	['B-CORP', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	wizkids has released collectible miniatures of the turrets , cores and companion cube ( s ) within the game .
['a', 'year', 'later', 'the', 'same', 'port', 'was', 'released', 'on', 'xbox', 'one', 'and', 'playstation', '4', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PROD', 'I-PROD', 'O', 'B-PROD', 'I-PROD', 'O']	a year later the same port was released on xbox one and playstation 4 .
"['many', 'of', 'the', 'bureau', ""'s"", 'designs', 'were', 'or', 'are', 'produced', 'at', 'motor', 'sich', ',', 'located', 'at', 'zaporizhzhia', 'international', 'airport', '.']"	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-CORP', 'I-CORP', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-LOC', 'I-LOC', 'I-LOC', 'O']	many of the bureau 's designs were or are produced at motor sich , located at zaporizhzhia international airport .
['the', 'brick', 'building', 'has', 'a', 'stucco', 'façade', 'and', 'a', 'slate', 'roof', 'with', 'a', 'gable', 'end', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PROD', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	the brick building has a stucco façade and a slate roof with a gable end .
['black-eyed', 'pea', 'are', 'also', 'part', 'of', 'the', 'diet', '.']	['B-PROD', 'I-PROD', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	black-eyed pea are also part of the diet .
['the', 'two', 'lower', 'stories', 'are', 'in', 'brick', 'and', 'the', 'upper', 'stories', 'in', 'half', 'timbering', 'and', 'stucco', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PROD', 'O']	the two lower stories are in brick and the upper stories in half timbering and stucco .
['he', 'presented', 'them', 'to', 'the', 'spain', 'monarchs', ',', 'though', 'by', 'then', 'the', 'young', 'were', 'lost', 'and', 'the', 'female', 'had', 'died', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-LOC', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	he presented them to the spain monarchs , though by then the young were lost and the female had died .
['goguryeo', 'met', 'major', 'setbacks', 'and', 'defeats', 'during', 'the', 'reign', 'of', 'gogugwon', 'in', 'the', '4th', 'century', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PER', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	goguryeo met major setbacks and defeats during the reign of gogugwon in the 4th century .
['he', 'joined', 'cardiff', 'rfc', 'for', 'the', '1990', '/', '91', 'season', '.']	['O', 'O', 'B-GRP', 'I-GRP', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	he joined cardiff rfc for the 1990 / 91 season .
['the', 'recording', 'by', 'christopher', 'hogwood', 'conducting', 'the', 'academy', 'of', 'ancient', 'music', 'also', 'omits', 'a', 'harpsichord', 'melody', 'in', 'the', 'third', 'movement', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O', 'O', 'B-GRP', 'I-GRP', 'I-GRP', 'I-GRP', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	the recording by christopher hogwood conducting the academy of ancient music also omits a harpsichord melody in the third movement .
