tokens	ner_tags	text
['it', 'has', 'since', 'been', 'released', 'on', 'dvd', 'in', 'its', 'correct', 'format', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PROD', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	it has since been released on dvd in its correct format .
['pouzilhac', 'is', 'a', 'commune', 'of', 'france', 'in', 'the', 'gard', 'department', 'of', 'france', 'in', 'southern', 'france', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'B-LOC', 'I-LOC', 'I-LOC', 'O', 'O', 'B-LOC', 'B-LOC', 'I-LOC', 'I-LOC', 'O', 'O', 'B-LOC', 'O']	pouzilhac is a commune of france in the gard department of france in southern france .
['for', 'five', 'voices', '(', 'coburg', ':', 'kaspar', 'bertsch', ')', ',', 'a', 'epithalamium']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-CW']	for five voices ( coburg : kaspar bertsch ) , a epithalamium
['his', 'nomination', 'for', 'election', 'to', 'the', 'royal', 'society', 'reads', ':']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-GRP', 'I-GRP', 'O', 'O']	his nomination for election to the royal society reads :
['often', 'theyre', 'served', 'with', 'borscht', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PROD', 'O']	often theyre served with borscht .
['her', 'maternal', 'grandfather', 'was', 'the', 'painter', 'john', 'la', 'farge', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'I-PER', 'O']	her maternal grandfather was the painter john la farge .
['he', 'was', 'banned', 'from', 'switzerland', 'for', 'five', 'years', 'and', 'was', 'given', 'a', 'conditional', 'fine', 'of', '(', 'in', '2017', ')', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-LOC', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	he was banned from switzerland for five years and was given a conditional fine of ( in 2017 ) .
['#', 'hot', 'in', 'herre', '(', 'remix', ')', '–', '3', ':', '45']	['O', 'B-CW', 'I-CW', 'I-CW', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	# hot in herre ( remix ) – 3 : 45
['the', 'use', 'of', 'concurrent', 'processes', 'which', 'communicate', 'through', 'message', 'passing', 'has', 'its', 'roots', 'in', 'operating', 'system', 'architectures', 'studied', 'in', 'the', '1960s', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-CW', 'I-CW', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	the use of concurrent processes which communicate through message passing has its roots in operating system architectures studied in the 1960s .
['front', 'suspension', 'for', 'both', 'the', 'turn', 'key', 'and', 'kit', 'car', 'was', 'provided', 'by', 'using', 'a', 'complete', 'front', 'subframe', 'from', 'a', 'chevrolet', 'corvair', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PROD', 'I-PROD', 'O']	front suspension for both the turn key and kit car was provided by using a complete front subframe from a chevrolet corvair .
['luis', 'castañeda', 'lossio', ',', 'lawyer', 'and', '2000', 'presidential', 'nominee', '–', 'national', 'solidarity', 'party']	['B-PER', 'I-PER', 'I-PER', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-GRP', 'I-GRP', 'I-GRP']	luis castañeda lossio , lawyer and 2000 presidential nominee – national solidarity party
['she', 'recited', 'an', 'original', 'composition', 'calling', 'for', 'an', 'institution', 'for', 'educating', 'the', 'blind', 'in', 'every', 'state', 'which', 'was', 'praised', 'by', 'john', 'quincy', 'adams', ',', 'among', 'others', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'I-PER', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	she recited an original composition calling for an institution for educating the blind in every state which was praised by john quincy adams , among others .
['he', 'continued', 'his', 'career', 'in', 'academia', 'by', 'teaching', 'at', 'west', 'virginia', 'university', ',', 'where', 'he', 'also', 'served', 'as', 'acting', 'president', '1876', '1877', '.', '[', '4', ']']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-GRP', 'I-GRP', 'I-GRP', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	he continued his career in academia by teaching at west virginia university , where he also served as acting president 1876 1877 . [ 4 ]
['it', 'is', 'published', 'by', 'success', '(', 'japan', ')', 'and', 'atlus', '(', 'north', 'america', ')', 'and', 'developed', 'by', 'tamsoft', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-CORP', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-CORP', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-CORP', 'O']	it is published by success ( japan ) and atlus ( north america ) and developed by tamsoft .
['he', 'was', 'born', 'in', 'copenhagen', 'and', 'worked', 'for', 'two', 'decades', 'for', 'the', 'publishing', 'house', 'gyldendal', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-LOC', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-GRP', 'O']	he was born in copenhagen and worked for two decades for the publishing house gyldendal .
['code', 'télévision', 'algérienne']	['O', 'B-CORP', 'I-CORP']	code télévision algérienne
['because', 'airliner', 'fly', 'at', 'very', 'high', 'altitudes', ',', 'the', 'cabin', 'must', 'be', 'pressurized', 'to', 'provide', 'a', 'safe', 'quantity', 'of', 'breathable', 'oxygen', 'to', 'passengers', 'and', 'crew', '.']	['O', 'B-PROD', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	because airliner fly at very high altitudes , the cabin must be pressurized to provide a safe quantity of breathable oxygen to passengers and crew .
['it', 'competed', 'in', 'its', 'first', 'season', 'in', 'the', 'newly', 'formed', 'mountain', 'west', 'conference', 'and', 'finished', 'with', 'a', '6', '–', '5', 'record', 'overall', 'and', 'a', '2', '–', '5', 'record', 'in', 'conference', 'games', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-GRP', 'I-GRP', 'I-GRP', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	it competed in its first season in the newly formed mountain west conference and finished with a 6 – 5 record overall and a 2 – 5 record in conference games .
['it', 'has', 'been', 'proposed', 'to', 'perform', 'laser', 'spectroscopy', 'of', 'the', '229th', 'nucleus', 'and', 'use', 'the', 'low', 'energy', 'transition', 'for', 'the', 'development', 'of', 'a', 'nuclear', 'clock', 'of', 'extremely', 'high', 'accuracy', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PROD', 'I-PROD', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	it has been proposed to perform laser spectroscopy of the 229th nucleus and use the low energy transition for the development of a nuclear clock of extremely high accuracy .
['the', 'program', 'provides', 'substantial', 'airtime', 'to', 'pro', 'israel', 'christian', 'organizations', 'such', 'as', 'the', 'international', 'christian', 'embassy', 'jerusalem', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-CORP', 'I-CORP', 'I-CORP', 'I-CORP', 'O']	the program provides substantial airtime to pro israel christian organizations such as the international christian embassy jerusalem .
['sitwell', 'makes', 'a', 'minor', 'appearance', 'in', 'the', '2012', 'film', 'the', 'avengers', ',']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-CW', 'I-CW', 'O']	sitwell makes a minor appearance in the 2012 film the avengers ,
['usa', 'laurel', 'hubbard']	['O', 'B-PER', 'I-PER']	usa laurel hubbard
['savigné-lévêque', 'mi']	['B-LOC', 'O']	savigné-lévêque mi
['she', 'was', 'the', 'chairman', 'of', 'the', 'standing', 'commission', 'on', 'the', 'history', 'of', 'cartography', 'of', 'the', 'international', 'cartographic', 'association', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-GRP', 'I-GRP', 'I-GRP', 'O']	she was the chairman of the standing commission on the history of cartography of the international cartographic association .
['some', 'of', 'them', 'were', 'gradually', 'replaced', 'during', 'the', '1920s', ',', 'with', 'fritz', 'schumacher', 'in', 'particular', 'establishing', 'a', 'brick', 'arch', 'prototype', 'for', 'many', 'bridges', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	some of them were gradually replaced during the 1920s , with fritz schumacher in particular establishing a brick arch prototype for many bridges .
['bernardini', ',', 'safe', 'manufacturer', 'which', 'operated', 'from', '1912', 'to', '1992']	['B-CORP', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	bernardini , safe manufacturer which operated from 1912 to 1992
['at', 'the', 'time', 'of', 'a', 'build', ',', 'it', 'will', 'generate', 'c#', ',', 'asp.net', ',', 'and', 'asp.net', 'files', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-CW', 'O', 'O', 'B-CW', 'O', 'O']	at the time of a build , it will generate c# , asp.net , and asp.net files .
['#', '–', 'andré', '(', 'armenian', 'representative', 'in', 'the', 'eurovision', 'song', 'contest', '2006', ')']	['O', 'O', 'B-PER', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-CW', 'I-CW', 'I-CW', 'I-CW', 'O']	# – andré ( armenian representative in the eurovision song contest 2006 )
['he', 'also', 'played', 'in', 'mestis', 'for', 'lempäälän', 'kisa', ',', 'kiekko-laser', 'and', 'jokipojat', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-GRP', 'O', 'B-GRP', 'I-GRP', 'O', 'B-GRP', 'O', 'B-GRP', 'O']	he also played in mestis for lempäälän kisa , kiekko-laser and jokipojat .
['since', 'completion', 'of', 'his', 'graduate', 'studies', ',', 'he', 'has', 'worked', 'at', 'goldman', 'sachs', 'investment', 'banking', 'company', 'in', 'the', 'field', 'of', 'risk', 'management', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-CORP', 'I-CORP', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	since completion of his graduate studies , he has worked at goldman sachs investment banking company in the field of risk management .
['it', 'was', 'started', 'in', '1906', 'by', 'v.', 'o.', 'chidambaram', 'billai', 'to', 'compete', 'against', 'the', 'monopoly', 'of', 'the', 'british-india', 'steam', 'navigation', 'company', '(', 'bisnc', ')', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'I-PER', 'I-PER', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-CORP', 'I-CORP', 'I-CORP', 'I-CORP', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	it was started in 1906 by v. o. chidambaram billai to compete against the monopoly of the british-india steam navigation company ( bisnc ) .
"['sebastian', ""'s"", 'death', 'was', 'depicted', 'in', 'the', '1949', 'film', 'fabiola', ',', 'in', 'which', 'he', 'was', 'played', 'by', 'massimo', 'girotti', '.']"	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-CW', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O']	sebastian 's death was depicted in the 1949 film fabiola , in which he was played by massimo girotti .
['file', ':', '97e38', 'hofmeisterkink', '.', 'jpg', '|', 'hofmeister', 'kink', 'on', 'an', 'bmw', '7', 'series']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PROD', 'I-PROD', 'I-PROD']	file : 97e38 hofmeisterkink . jpg | hofmeister kink on an bmw 7 series
['turkish', 'airlines', 'was', 'featured', 'in', 'the', 'film', 'batman', 'v', 'superman:', 'dawn', 'of', 'justice', '.']	['B-CORP', 'I-CORP', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-CW', 'I-CW', 'I-CW', 'I-CW', 'I-CW', 'I-CW', 'O']	turkish airlines was featured in the film batman v superman: dawn of justice .
['in', '2006', ',', 'he', 'moved', 'to', 'oita', 'trinita', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-GRP', 'I-GRP', 'O']	in 2006 , he moved to oita trinita .
['#', 'rhinestone', 'cowboy', '(', 'larry', 'weiss', ')', '3', ':', '15']	['O', 'B-CW', 'I-CW', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	# rhinestone cowboy ( larry weiss ) 3 : 15
['it', 'is', 'served', 'by', 'koleje', 'mazowieckie', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-CORP', 'I-CORP', 'O']	it is served by koleje mazowieckie .
['the', 'discovery', 'of', 'a', 'cruciform', 'shaped', 'baptismal', 'font', 'confirms', 'that', 'the', 'building', 'was', 'used', 'as', 'a', 'baptistery', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PROD', 'I-PROD', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	the discovery of a cruciform shaped baptismal font confirms that the building was used as a baptistery .
['aconit', 'in', 'grenoble', 'has', 'a', 'complete', '1130', 'system', '.']	['O', 'O', 'B-LOC', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	aconit in grenoble has a complete 1130 system .
['daniele', 'bracciali', '/', 'oliver', 'marach', 'def', '.', 'marin', 'draganja', '/', 'mate', 'pavić', '6', '–', '3', ',', '2', '–', '6', ',', '[', '11', '–', '9', ']']	['B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O', 'O', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	daniele bracciali / oliver marach def . marin draganja / mate pavić 6 – 3 , 2 – 6 , [ 11 – 9 ]
['mcphatter', 'later', 'became', 'lead', 'singer', 'of', 'the', 'drifters', ',', 'and', 'then', 'a', 'solo', 'star', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-GRP', 'I-GRP', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	mcphatter later became lead singer of the drifters , and then a solo star .
['as', 'to', 'the', 'fate', 'of', 'the', 'princes', ',', 'it', 'is', 'widely', 'held', 'that', 'richard', 'iii', 'of', 'england', 'ordered', 'the', 'death', 'of', 'his', 'two', 'nephews', 'to', 'secure', 'his', 'own', 'reign', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'I-PER', 'I-PER', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	as to the fate of the princes , it is widely held that richard iii of england ordered the death of his two nephews to secure his own reign .
['he', 'has', 'previously', 'represented', 'the', 'afghanistan', 'national', 'cricket', 'team', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-GRP', 'I-GRP', 'I-GRP', 'I-GRP', 'O']	he has previously represented the afghanistan national cricket team .
['the', 'team', 'lost', 'their', 'first', 'round', 'pick', 'in', '2001', 'to', 'the', 'cleveland', 'indians', 'as', 'compensation', 'for', 'signing', 'free', 'agent', 'manny', 'ramirez', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-GRP', 'I-GRP', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O']	the team lost their first round pick in 2001 to the cleveland indians as compensation for signing free agent manny ramirez .
['his', 'ideal', ',', 'often', 'misunderstood', 'even', 'today', 'was', 'to', 'bring', 'about', 'a', 'union', 'of', 'the', 'churches', ',', 'which', 'rome', 'and', 'constantinople', 'had', 'tried', 'to', 'do', 'without', 'success', 'for', 'centuries', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-LOC', 'O', 'B-LOC', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	his ideal , often misunderstood even today was to bring about a union of the churches , which rome and constantinople had tried to do without success for centuries .
['it', 'is', 'a', 'spin', 'off', 'of', 'the', 'freeform', 'show', 'the', 'fosters', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-CORP', 'O', 'B-CW', 'I-CW', 'O']	it is a spin off of the freeform show the fosters .
['the', 'car', 'is', 'intended', 'to', 'fit', 'between', 'the', 'škoda', 'fabia', 'and', 'the', 'škoda', 'octavia', ',', 'and', 'to', 'be', 'a', 'competitor', 'to', 'the', 'cars', 'in', 'the', 'c-segment', 'hatchback', 'segment', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PROD', 'I-PROD', 'O', 'O', 'B-PROD', 'I-PROD', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PROD', 'O', 'O', 'O']	the car is intended to fit between the škoda fabia and the škoda octavia , and to be a competitor to the cars in the c-segment hatchback segment .
['born', ':', 'don', 'king', ',', 'boxing', 'promoter', ',', 'in', 'cleveland', ',', 'ohio']	['O', 'O', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-LOC', 'O', 'B-LOC']	born : don king , boxing promoter , in cleveland , ohio
['the', 'present', 'musical', 'style', 'is', 'derived', 'from', 'non', 'traditional', 'musical', 'accompaniment', 'to', 'the', 'riffs', 'of', 'punjab', 'called', 'by', 'the', 'same', 'name', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-LOC', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	the present musical style is derived from non traditional musical accompaniment to the riffs of punjab called by the same name .
['besides', 'sharing', 'a', 'title', 'and', 'the', 'premise', 'of', 'female', 'rivalry', ',', 'this', 'drama', 'has', 'nothing', 'to', 'do', 'with', 'the', 'all', 'about', 'eve', 'starring', 'bette', 'davis', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-CW', 'I-CW', 'I-CW', 'O', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O']	besides sharing a title and the premise of female rivalry , this drama has nothing to do with the all about eve starring bette davis .
['the', 'movie', 'traffic', 'explores', 'both', 'sides', 'of', 'this', '.']	['O', 'O', 'B-CW', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	the movie traffic explores both sides of this .
['the', 'fruit', 'is', 'a', 'lantern', 'like', 'inflated', 'sphere', 'ribbed', 'into', 'segments', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PROD', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	the fruit is a lantern like inflated sphere ribbed into segments .
['file', ':', 'nasi', 'campur', 'rawon', '.', 'jpg', '|', 'nasi', 'campur', 'with', 'rawon', 'from', 'surabaya']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PROD', 'O', 'B-LOC']	file : nasi campur rawon . jpg | nasi campur with rawon from surabaya
['since', '1999', 'the', 'size', 'of', 'a', 'sheet', 'has', 'been', 'shrinking', ';', 'kimberly-clark', 'reduced', 'the', 'length', 'of', 'a', 'sheet', 'to', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-CORP', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	since 1999 the size of a sheet has been shrinking ; kimberly-clark reduced the length of a sheet to .
['it', 'was', 'released', 'as', 'the', 'lead', 'single', 'from', 'her', 'third', 'album', ',', 'am', 'i', 'not', 'your', 'girl?', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-CW', 'I-CW', 'I-CW', 'I-CW', 'I-CW', 'O']	it was released as the lead single from her third album , am i not your girl? .
['chris', 'cole', ',', 'former', 'wide', 'receiver', 'for', 'the', 'denver', 'broncos', '.']	['B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-GRP', 'I-GRP', 'O']	chris cole , former wide receiver for the denver broncos .
['he', 'has', 'played', 'briefly', 'in', 'the', 'national', 'hockey', 'league', 'with', 'the', 'pittsburgh', 'penguins', 'and', 'the', 'arizona', 'coyotes', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-CORP', 'I-CORP', 'I-CORP', 'O', 'O', 'B-GRP', 'I-GRP', 'O', 'O', 'B-GRP', 'I-GRP', 'O']	he has played briefly in the national hockey league with the pittsburgh penguins and the arizona coyotes .
['sportfreunde', 'stuttgart', ',', 'promoted', 'from', '2nd', 'division']	['B-GRP', 'I-GRP', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	sportfreunde stuttgart , promoted from 2nd division
['battle', 'hymn', 'directed', 'by', 'douglas', 'sirk']	['B-CW', 'I-CW', 'O', 'O', 'B-PER', 'I-PER']	battle hymn directed by douglas sirk
['their', 'dkw', 'rt', '125', 'was', 'one', 'of', 'the', 'first', 'motor', 'vehicles', 'to', 'achieve', 'over', '100', 'mpg', 'as', 'a', 'result', '.']	['O', 'B-PROD', 'I-PROD', 'I-PROD', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	their dkw rt 125 was one of the first motor vehicles to achieve over 100 mpg as a result .
['radio', 'rossii', '–', 'talk', 'radio', 'and', 'regional', 'programming']	['B-CORP', 'I-CORP', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	radio rossii – talk radio and regional programming
['it', 'stars', 'stephen', 'lang', ',', 'luke', 'pasqualino', ',', 'om', 'puri', 'and', 'vinnie', 'jones', '.']	['O', 'O', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O']	it stars stephen lang , luke pasqualino , om puri and vinnie jones .
['due', 'to', 'the', 'fact', 'that', 'there', 'are', 'two', 'different', 'materials', 'in', 'dfsw', ';', 'formation', 'of', 'a', 'composite', 'material', 'structure', 'within', 'the', 'nugget', 'zone', 'is', 'inevitable', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PROD', 'I-PROD', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	due to the fact that there are two different materials in dfsw ; formation of a composite material structure within the nugget zone is inevitable .
['apple', 'inc.', 'used', 'a', 'number', 'of', 'c&t', 'controllers', 'in', 'their', 'powerbook', 'line', '.']	['B-CORP', 'I-CORP', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PROD', 'O', 'O']	apple inc. used a number of c&t controllers in their powerbook line .
['in', '2007', ',', 'he', 'was', 'nominated', 'for', 'a', 'british', 'computer', 'society', 'award', 'for', 'accessibility', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-GRP', 'I-GRP', 'I-GRP', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	in 2007 , he was nominated for a british computer society award for accessibility .
['he', 'was', 'a', 'younger', 'son', 'of', 'hugh', 'i,', 'count', 'of', 'blois', 'and', 'mary,', 'countess', 'of', 'blois', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'I-PER', 'I-PER', 'I-PER', 'O', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'I-PER', 'I-PER', 'O']	he was a younger son of hugh i, count of blois and mary, countess of blois .
['in', '1780', 'he', 'enrolled', 'in', 'the', 'secondary', 'school', 'attached', 'to', 'moscow', 'state', 'university', 'from', 'which', 'he', 'graduated', 'in', '1785', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-GRP', 'I-GRP', 'O', 'O', 'B-GRP', 'I-GRP', 'I-GRP', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	in 1780 he enrolled in the secondary school attached to moscow state university from which he graduated in 1785 .
['she', 'was', 'the', 'granddaughter', 'of', 'former', 'major', 'league', 'baseball', 'player', 'and', 'manager', 'dallas', 'green', 'and', 'the', 'second', 'cousin', 'of', 'actress', 'sophia', 'bush', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-CORP', 'I-CORP', 'I-CORP', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O']	she was the granddaughter of former major league baseball player and manager dallas green and the second cousin of actress sophia bush .
['until', '1970', ',', 'it', 'was', 'also', 'the', 'standard', 'used', 'in', 'juvenile', 'court', 'in', 'the', 'united', 'states', 'of', 'america', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-LOC', 'I-LOC', 'I-LOC', 'I-LOC', 'O']	until 1970 , it was also the standard used in juvenile court in the united states of america .
['tyrone', 'spong', 'did', 'not', 'know', 'that', 'and', 'does', 'not', 'like', 'it', 'as', 'well', '.']	['B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	tyrone spong did not know that and does not like it as well .
['he', 'has', 'formerly', 'played', 'in', 'the', 'national', 'hockey', 'league', '(', 'nhl', ')', 'with', 'the', 'new', 'jersey', 'devils', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-CORP', 'I-CORP', 'I-CORP', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-GRP', 'I-GRP', 'I-GRP', 'O']	he has formerly played in the national hockey league ( nhl ) with the new jersey devils .
['engaged', 'in', 'escorting', 'trains', 'and', 'u.s.', 'mail', 'coaches', 'on', 'the', 'santa', 'fe', 'trail', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-LOC', 'I-LOC', 'I-LOC', 'O']	engaged in escorting trains and u.s. mail coaches on the santa fe trail .
['one', 'the', 'days', 'passed', ',', 'the', 'child', 'would', 'be', 'gifted', 'a', 'name', 'and', 'a', 'bulla', 'during', 'a', 'ceremony', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PROD', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	one the days passed , the child would be gifted a name and a bulla during a ceremony .
['she', 'recorded', 'a', 'remake', 'of', 'strawberry', 'fields', 'forever', 'by', 'the', 'beatles', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-CW', 'I-CW', 'I-CW', 'O', 'B-GRP', 'I-GRP', 'O']	she recorded a remake of strawberry fields forever by the beatles .
['the', 'much', 'earlier', 'honda', 'xlv', '750', 'r', 'was', 'a', 'shaft', 'driven', 'motorcycle', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PROD', 'I-PROD', 'I-PROD', 'I-PROD', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	the much earlier honda xlv 750 r was a shaft driven motorcycle .
['other', 'scenes', 'depicting', 'the', 'same', 'train', 'were', 'filmed', 'with', 'a', 'drg', 'class', '86', 'tank', 'engine', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PROD', 'I-PROD', 'I-PROD', 'O', 'O', 'O']	other scenes depicting the same train were filmed with a drg class 86 tank engine .
['william', 'parker,', '4th', 'baron', 'monteagle', 'name', 'was', 'also', 'mentioned', ',', 'by', 'a', 'worried', 'francis', 'tresham', '.']	['B-PER', 'I-PER', 'I-PER', 'I-PER', 'I-PER', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O']	william parker, 4th baron monteagle name was also mentioned , by a worried francis tresham .
['as', 'suggested', 'by', 'its', 'title', ',', 'a', 'homage', 'to', 'jack', 'finney', '1955', 'science', 'fiction', 'novel', 'the', 'body', 'snatchers', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-CW', 'I-CW', 'I-CW', 'O']	as suggested by its title , a homage to jack finney 1955 science fiction novel the body snatchers .
['the', 'building', 'is', 'designated', 'by', 'english', 'heritage', 'as', 'a', 'grade', 'ii', '*', 'listed', 'building', 'in', 'the', 'united', 'kingdom', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-GRP', 'I-GRP', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-LOC', 'I-LOC', 'I-LOC', 'I-LOC', 'I-LOC', 'I-LOC', 'O']	the building is designated by english heritage as a grade ii * listed building in the united kingdom .
['gems', 'is', 'the', 'twelfth', 'studio', 'album', 'by', 'united', 'states', 'of', 'america', 'singer', 'patti', 'labelle', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-LOC', 'I-LOC', 'I-LOC', 'I-LOC', 'O', 'B-PER', 'I-PER', 'O']	gems is the twelfth studio album by united states of america singer patti labelle .
['the', 'game', 'has', 'started', 'a', 'gran', 'turismo', ',', 'and', 'has', 'spawned', 'over', '10', 'spin-off', 'and', 'sequels', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-CW', 'I-CW', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-PROD', 'O', 'O', 'O']	the game has started a gran turismo , and has spawned over 10 spin-off and sequels .
